(Penny:)...and want to marry
Howard wolowitz?
- I do, with all my heart.
- Tsk, got it. Just had to check.
(Amy:)He's great.
(Leonard:)All right, Sheldon.
We're going to Wil's.
(Leonard:)- This is your last chance.
- No, Leonard, this is your last chance.
(Sheldon:)One day, a historian
is going to come to you and say:
"ls it true you were friends
with Dr. Sheldon Cooper?"
(Sheldon:)And you're going to have to choke back
a hot sob of regret and humiliation...
(Sheldon:)...as you mumble,
"l was, but I chose to go to a party...
(Sheldon:)...thrown by the one kid from
Stand By Me that no one remembers."
- You want to drive?
- Sure.
- Hey, Sheldon?
- Oh, good. You picked me, you picked me.
(Leonard:)No, I just got a text from Stuart.
Brent Spiner is at the party.